Every Life Is Worth Saving.
We Die Young is a drama, action, crime film directed by Lior Geller.
Lucas, a 14-year-old boy inducted into the gang life in Washington D.C., is
determined that his 10-year-old brother won't follow the same path.
When an Afghanistan war veteran comes into the
neighborhood, an opportunity arises.
Daniel, played by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Rincon, played by David Castañeda.
Anna, played by Joana Metrass.
Lucas, played by Elijah Rodriguez.
Miguel, played by Nicholas Sean Johnny.
Jester, played by Charlie MacGechan.
We Die Young is a 2019 American direct-to-video action film directed by Lior Geller, and
starring Jean-Claude Van Damme, David Castañeda, and Elijah Rodriguez.
The tone is emotional and intense.